const questions = [
    {
        question : "what is 2+2",
        answer : "4",
        option:{
            option1:"2",
            option2:"4",
            option3:"22",
            option4:"0",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 6+3",
        answer : "9",
        option:{
            option1:"21",
            option2:"4",
            option3:"9",
            option4:"13",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 12-8",
        answer : "4",
        option:{
            option1:"-4",
            option2:"43",
            option3:"4",
            option4:"1",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 12+6",
        answer : "18",
        option:{
            option1:"18",
            option2:"21",
            option3:"20",
            option4:"6",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 2*10",
        answer : "20",
        option:{
            option1:"10",
            option2:"5",
            option3:"100",
            option4:"20",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 12+6",
        answer : "18",
        option:{
            option1:"18",
            option2:"21",
            option3:"20",
            option4:"6",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 200/2",
        answer : "100",
        option:{
            option1:"100",
            option2:"4",
            option3:"22",
            option4:"0",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 2+9",
        answer : "11",
        option:{
            option1:"2",
            option2:"11",
            option3:"22",
            option4:"0",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 2+2",
        answer : "4",
        option:{
            option1:"2",
            option2:"4",
            option3:"22",
            option4:"0",
        }
    },
    {
        question : "what is 2*10",
        answer : "20",
        option:{
            option1:"10",
            option2:"5",
            option3:"100",
            option4:"20",
        }
    },
]

 

export default questions;